papaki.com 2015-11-02

# Privacy Policy | papaki.com

The management and protection of all personal information of the users/visitors that use Papaki.com services are met according to the European beneficiary (guidelines 95/46/EK and 97/66/EK). The current legislations take into consideration the vast and rapid increase of technology and specifically Internet regarding privacy policies. For that apparent reason, in case of any changes or modifications, Papaki.com will adjust accordingly. Papaki.com has the right and privilege to change and modify these terms and inform all of its visitors and users in the same time. If someone does not agree to the privacy terms and conditions, he/she should not use the services provided by this site.

 **Personal information which Papaki.com requests are:**

Personal Data: Each visitor can visit and look into the site without having to provide any personal information. However, if someone decides to buy one of our products he/she will have to provide his/her email address and password.

Information regarding the sale of services and products: The mandatory information for your every transaction is first and last name, telephone number, full address (street number and name, city, zip code) type of receipt, normal receipt or invoice. Sometimes we might ask you for your mobile phone number or fax number just in case we need to contact you as soon as possible.

Invoice data: **** In case you request an invoice, the information you will have to provide to us are: name of company, VAT number, and address of the company.Contact via Live Chat: When contacting Papaki.gr via live chat, the information we collect is your name, address email, the IP, the date and time of the communication and the text exchanged in this communication. These data are collected for better customer service and for security purposes.

 **Links**

Papaki.com includes links towards other sites that are not checked and verified by the site itself. Papaki is not in charge in case these sites do not follow the terms and conditions regarding privacy policies

 **IP Addresses**

The IP addresses from which a PC has access to the computer and then to the Papaki.com website is used only for statistical purposes and to make sure that all transactions are secure.

 **Cookies**

Most major companies in order to provide personalized support and services, use alphanumeric recognition files called cookies. They are characterized into two types, permanent and session cookies: Permanent cookies remain in your hard disk after you finish your visit, keeping information that will be used once you visit our site next time. Session cookies are used to recognize that you have entered inside the website, without having to be asked for information such as email and password each time you want to complete a transaction. These are automatically erased once you leave the website. Papaki.com uses session cookies, so that we don’t have to ask you for your email and password each time you enter in our online store.

 **General Terms for personal data protection.**

Papaki.com is in charge of keeping and storing your personal information and not giving it out to others unless it has been requested by court order or other authorities.

Papaki.com keeps and stores data with your personal information which has been sent from the visitor/user for communication, accounting and financial reasons.

Every user/customer can come in contact with the corresponding department in order to check whether there is a personal file and change it, correct it or even delete it.

Papaki.com, specifically its marketing department, can use the provided information for statistical, financial so it can improve its services and feedback.

Each time you visit the Papaki.com website, in order to proceed to an order of products or services, or even so we can come in contact with you, you must provide us with your personal information such as name, occupation, email address etc. Any personal information you provide us with via the Papaki.com website are only used for Papaki.com services and not others according to the law regarding personal data legislation. The Papaki.com online store works according to the current laws and legislations and keeps all of your personal information with absolutely safety up to the point that you are still a customer of Papaki.com. All personal information you provide in Papaki.com is used by the website and online store, or even by companies that work with the pre-mentioned companies and providers. All information you provide us with is noticed legally to all responsible court, police and other ministerial offices according to the current laws and legislations. The client has the right, according to the legislation regarding private and discrete information of telecommunications, to accept or deny according to law.
